07031194041 davidadrian759@gmail.com

41, Shosanya street, Ijegun, Ikotun, Lagos.

DAVID ASUQUO, EFFIONG

B.Sc Pure and Industrial Chemistry (University of Port-Harcourt, Choba)

Well trained ICT specialist with mid level experience in technology operations. Area of expertise Include web development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React), Graphic Design, Digital Marketing and Software development. Tech savvy and strategic team player. Versed in a range of Modern technologies, solutions and development.

PERSONAL DATA

Gender

Marital Status

State of Origin

L.G.A

Nationality

Male

Single

Akwa Ibom

Uyo

Nigerian

SKILLS

- Quick learner
- Digital Marketing
- Graphic Design
- Critical thinking
- Team Player
- Outstanding Communication Skills
- Client Relationships
- Microsoft Office Proficient
- Research and Analysis
- Analytical skills
- Good managerial skills
- Driving (License)

EMPLOYMENT

2018-2020

DACOTA RESTAURANT (204, Obiwali Rd, Rumuigo, Port Harcourt, Rivers state).

ADMINISTRATOR/ HEAD SUPERVISOR

- Digital Marketer
- Administrative running of the restaurant.
- Supervising production(Quality control)
- ICT administrator.

2016- 2017	MEFFIO TECHNOLOGY (5, Thompson Avenue beside Genesis Restaurant, Woji, PH)
	TECHNOLOGIST
	 Design of board and chipset for production Soldering and evaluation of finished products for testing. Board assembling.
2014-2015	INTELS NIG LTD. (Onne, PH)
	INDUSTRIAL ATTACHMENT
	Assistant Human Resources Manager(CHO)Store Manager(CHO)
EDUCATION	
2011-2015	UNIVERSITY OF PORT-HARCOURT, CHOBA.
	B.Sc in Pure and Industrial Chemistry.
2015-2018	SOFT-TOUCH COMPUTER INSTITUTE, ABA ROAD, PH.
	Certificate in Advance Embedded designs
	Certificate in Graphic technology
	Certificate in Networking
QUALIFICATIONS	
	- B.Sc in Pure and Industrial Chemistry.
	- Certification in Graphic Designs
	- Certification in Office Suites (Orlean Investment,Onne)
	 Certification in Digital Marketing (Google) Software Development and Programming (in-view).
	Software Development and Programming (in view).
REFEREES	
	Mrs. IDONGESIT EMMANUEL ITIABA 08028355577
	Coordinator, NYSC, Akwa Ibom state.
	Mr. MATTHEW OPEYEMI 08035784351
	NEPZA NIG PLC.